

MARTIN RENÉ LARIOS SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER

CONTACT INFO

- +505 8430 0844
- mrlarios_1994@hotmail.es
- in martin-larios
- 💡 Managua, Nicaragua

EDUCATION

2013 - 2018

Bachelor Degree in System
Engineering
Universidad Nacional de Ingeniería

CERTIFICATIONS

2020

Scrum Foundation Professional Certificate CertiProf

2020

AWS Academy Cloud Foundations
BootCamp Institute

LANGUAGES

Spanish

English

PROFILE

I have over 5 years of experience working as a Software Developer, building websites and mobile apps using various technologies such as ReactJs, React Native, NextJs, GraphQL, NestJs, and ASP.net Framework. I also have experience integrating with third-party tools such as Salesforce, Jira, and Zendesk Agent.

Overall, I am a dedicated and driven individual with a passion for software development and a commitment to delivering high-quality work.

EXPERIENCE



ENGINEERING TEAM LEAD SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER

2022 - PRESENT | GROWTH ACCELERATION PARTNERS | AUSTIN, TEXAS, USA

At Growth Acceleration Partners, I currently working as a Senior Software Engineer, using ReactJs+Typescript+NextJs, React Native CLI+Typescript, GraphQL, ApolloClient, Docker, AWS to create and build new web sites and mobile apps besides this, as the Engineering Team Lead, my role is to provide guidance, direction, and support to a team of talented engineers. I am responsible for overseeing the day-to-day operations, ensuring that projects are completed efficiently and on time.



SOFTWARE ENGINEER

2021 - 2022 | NICASOURCE LLC | MANAGUA, NICARAGUA

I worked as a Software Engineer building websites and mobile apps using ReactJs+Typescript, React Native + Expo, Docker, AWS, NestJs+Typescript, Strapi Headless CMS.



APPLICATION SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

2019 - 2021 | LOGICAL DATA | SAN JOSÉ, COSTA RICA

As an Application Software Developer at Logical Data, I built websites and integrated SAP B1 using ReactJs, ASP.net Core 3.1, SAP SDK, Microsoft SQL Server, and Azure.



SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

2017 - 2019 | MSCORP | MANAGUA, NICARAGUA

I worked as a Software Developer building an ERP using ASP.net Framework, DevExpress, and Microsoft SQL Server.

SKILLS

